Kgothatso Mogale

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT GRADUATE

Die Hoewes, Centurion | 082-443-7085 | kgothatso.m1997@gmail.com

Summary

I am a Business Management Graduate (Ndip). I graduated from Rosebank College in 2019. Since then, I have gained work experience in Administration, Sales, and Customer Service. I have enrolled in a Software Engineering Program with ALX Africa, and I am due to graduate at the end of July 2024. I am driven, willing to learn, adaptable, and a good communicator. I am good at problem solving, managing time and tasks, and very reliable. I have a driver's license and access to a vehicle.

Experience

Game Retail Store | Retail Cashier

2022/11 - 2023/03

- Resolve customer complaints and queries.
- Record sales and process payments.
- Process refunds and discount purchases.
- Product promotion.

Department of Education | Administrative Intern

2020/11 - 2021/11

- Receive, Assess, Organize and File applications.
- Provide feedback on application outcomes.
- Respond to client queries and complaints.
- Financial bookkeeping.
- Assist with in-office inquiries.

News Café | Bartender

2020/01 - 2020/09

- Provide professional customer service.
- Fulfil customer requests.
- Process payments and refunds.
- Perform inventory duties.

Education

Rosebank College, Ndip Business Management

2019

Majors: Business Management, Computer Literacy, Entrepreneurship & Marketing.

Software Engineering Program, ALX Africa

2024

Majors: Python, C, JavaScript, Java, SQL | Specialization: Front-End Development.

References

- Desmond Nkambule | Department of Education | 082 562 7070
- Lungelo Ndlovu | Department of Education | 067 993 3356
- Josiah Ditshego | Department of Education | 073 134 8738